So I told Carl, nobody, no matter
how famous their parents are...
...is allowed to climb
on the dinosaur.
Of course, it went
right in one ear....
I love how he cares so much
about stuff.
If I squint, I can pretend
he's Alan Alda.
Oh, good. Another dinosaur story.
When are those gonna become extinct?
If I was a superhero who could fly
and be invisible...
... that would be the best.
What does Rachel see in this guy?
I love Rachel.
I wish she was my wife.
Who's singing?
The One With the Race Car Bed
When you guys were kids
and you played Happy Days...
...who were you?
I was Richie.
I was always Joanie.
Question: Was "Egg the Gellers!"
the war cry of your neighborhood?
It's the Mattress King!
Change the channel!
Wait! I want to see this!
After I divorce him...
...half of that kingdom
is gonna be mine!
Despair fills the mattress showroom.
My Kingdom is suddenly
without a Queen.
I'm so depressed...
...I'm going to slash...
...my prices!
Check it out!
599 for a California king!
499 for a pillow-top queen set!
I'm going medieval on prices!
What a wank!
I cannot believe he's using
our divorce to sell mattresses!
I know. At $499 for a pillow-top
queen, who cares about the divorce?
Those babies will sell themselves!
And I'm appalled for you, by the way.
I'm close! I'm cheap! I'm the King!
Okay, Daddy. We'll see you
tomorrow night. Okay, bye-bye.
"We"?
are having dinner with my Dad
tomorrow night. I hope that's okay.
Oh, shoot!
Tomorrow's not good.
I'm supposed to fall off
the Empire State Building...
...and land on a bicycle
with no seat, so....
My father doesn't hate you.
Please. He refers to me
as "Wet-Head."
Honey, he calls everybody
by a nickname.
I know. Just one dinner.
One night. For me. Please?
I just want him to love you like I do.
All right. Well, not exactly
like I do.
But if you do come to dinner...
...I'll love you like I do
in that black thing that you like.
I'll go.
Fine.
Thank you.
Hi, Gunther.
Yeah. We'll see.
Hey, you guys!
Guess what.
-I got a gig!
-Great!
That's why I can never be an actor.
I can't say "gig."
I can't say "croissant."
Oh, my God!
-What's the part?
-It's not a part.
I'm teaching Acting for Soap Operas
at the Learning Extension.
Come on! That's great!
It's my chance to give
something back...
...to the acting community.
You're probably not allowed to sleep
with your students.
I know.
I don't know, Monica.
It feels funny just being here.
If you buy a bed from
Janice's ex-husband...
...it's like betraying Chandler.
Not at these prices!
You know, in England this car would be
on the other side of the store.
Come here.
This is my new bed!
You gotta feel this bad boy!
Monica, it still feels so weird,
you know?
Chandler's your friend.
Oh, my God!
All right, take this bed.
You can make other friends.
Good evening.
I am Mr. Tribbiani.
And I will be teaching
Acting for Soap Operas.
Now...
...on my first day as Dr. Drake
Ramoray on Days Of Our Lives...
... I learned one of the most important
things in soap opera acting...
...is reacting.
This does not mean acting again.
It means you don't have a line,
but someone else just did.
And it goes something like this.
Thanks. Thanks a lot.
By the way, before I forget.
To work in soap operas...
...some of you will have to
become more attractive.
All right, moving right along....
-How was teaching last night?
-Great! You get to say stuff like...
... "Hey, the bell doesn't dismiss you.
I dismiss you."
Oh, nice.
Oh, and I got an audition
for All My Children!
It's this great part.
This boxer named Nick.
And I'm so, so right for it.
He's just like me.
Except that he's a boxer...
...and has an evil twin.
Hear ye, hear ye!
Delivery from the Mattress King!
You Miss Geller?
Sign here.
Do I have a middle name?
All right. Monica "Felula"...
...Geller.
It's that bedroom there.
Monica bought a bed
from the Mattress King?
Please, please, please
don't say anything to Chandler.
-You want me to lie to him?
-ls that a problem?
Oh, hey, "Nick the boxer."
Let's see what you got!
All right, put them up.
Hey, you're pretty good at this.
I had to learn.
I was staying at the "Y"...
...and some of the young men
weren't acting Christian enough.
Hey, now!
And I'm bleeding.
Okay, great.
Wow! And I'm a vegetarian!
I'm sorry.
We'll put some ice on it.
Put your head back.
-I can't see.
-I have you.
Oh, God!
Which bedroom do you want it in,
Ms. Geller?
It's the compulsively neat one
by the window.
Gotcha.
Hi, Daddy!
This is where they put us?
What? There was no table
in the kitchen?
-Hello, baby.
-You remember Ross.
Nice to see you again, Dr. Greene.
So!
-How's the library?
-Museum.
-What happened to the library?
-There never was a library.
I mean, there are libraries.
It's just...
...that I've never worked at one.
You know what's really good here?
The lobster.
-Shall I just order three?
-lf you're really hungry.
It was a joke. I made a joke.
Actually, Daddy,
Ross is allergic to lobster.
Who's allergic to lobster? I guess
someone that works in a library.
-It's
-I know. It's a museum!
You're the only who can make a joke?
At least mine was funny.
Waiter.
We will have two lobsters
and a menu.
So, Dr. Greene, how's the old boat?
They found rust. Do you know
what rust does to a boat?
Gives it a nice antique-y look?
Rust is boat cancer, Ross.
Wow, I'm sorry.
When I was a kid,
I lost a bike to that.
Excuse me for a moment.
I want to say good night
to the Levines before we go.
Honey, stop. It's not that bad.
Your dad must have added wrong.
He only tipped 4%.
Yeah. That's Daddy.
"That's Daddy"? Doesn't it
bother you? You're a waitress.
Yes, it bothers me.
If he was a regular at the coffee
house, I'd be serving him sneezers.
-So?
-So, Ross...
... I've bugged him about this
a million times. He won't change.
Do you really serve people sneezers?
Well, I don't.
All right, kids. Ready?
Thanks again, Dr. Greene.
Wait, I think I forgot my receipt.
-You don't need that.
-Why not?
The carbon. It's messy. I mean,
gets on your fingers and causes...
... night blindness.
What is this?
Who put a 20 down here?
Oh, yeah, that would be me.
I have a problem.
I tip way too much.
Way too much.
-It's a sickness, really.
-Yeah, it is.
-We have to do something about that.
-Excuse me.
You think I'm cheap?
He didn't mean anything by that.
He really didn't.
Nothing I do means anything. Really.
This is nice.
I pay $200 for dinner.
You put down $20 and you come out
looking like Mr. Big Shot.
You really want to be Mr. Big Shot?
Here.
I'll tell you what. You pay the
whole bill, Mr. Big Shot. All right?
Well, "Mr. Big Shot" is better
than "Wet-Head."
Okay, some tricks of the trade.
Now, I've never been able to cry
as an actor...
...so if I have to cry...
... I cut a hole in my pocket...
...take a pair of tweezers...
...and just start pulling.
Or let's say I want to convey...
...that I've just done
something evil.
That would be your basic I've-got-a-
fish-hook-in-my-eyebrow-and-l-like-it.
Let's say I've just gotten bad news.
Well, all I do there
is try and divide 232 by 13.
And that's how it's done.
Great soap opera acting
tonight, everybody.
Class dismissed.
Hey, Mr. Trib.
Guess what? I got an audition!
One of my students got an audition.
I'm so proud!
I was wondering if you'd
coach me for it.
You bet! What's the part?
Oh, it's great!
It's a role on All My Children.
Nick the boxer.
You couldn't leave it alone.
Four percent, okay? I tip more than
that when there's a bug in my food.
Tonight was about the two of you
getting along.
Would you just see
my chiropractor already?
I'm gonna go to a doctor who went
to medical school in a mini-mall.
Hey, Pheebs. What are you doing?
I'm freaking out!
Monica trusted me with something
and she shouldn't have!
I haven't lived here in a while,
so I have to ask you.
Does Monica still turn the lights on
in her room?
I am so dead!
Look, here's the bottom line.
This is fixable if we act fast, okay?
I'll invite him to brunch tomorrow,
and you can make nice.
Honey, I have tried to make nice.
It doesn't work.
Look, I realize my father
is difficult.
But that's why you have got to be
the bigger man here.
Sweetie, I could be the bigger man.
I could be the biggest man.
I could be a huge, giant man, and
it still wouldn't make a difference.
Except I could pick your father up and
say, "Like me! Like me, tiny doctor!"
Can't you just try it one more time?
For me? For me?
One brunch is not gonna
solve anything.
Face it.
We're never gonna get along.
Well, you are just going to have to.
I've already got a mother and father
who cannot stay in the same room.
I don't want to have a separate room
for you too!
I'll get the bagels.
What's this?
Isn't it cool?
This is not the bed I ordered.
I know! You must have won
a contest or something.
Why is this car in my bedroom?
I'm sorry. I wasn't looking...
...and the store won't take
it back, because you signed for it.
-When did I sign for it?
-When I was you.
It's all Joey's fault,
because he left his nose open!
Did you make brownies today?
IKnock, knock!
Quick! Take off your dress.
He won't notice the bed.
I'm going for sushi.
Does anybody want?
Somebody missed the off-ramp!
It's Monica's bed. What?
It's a racecar!
This has always been Monica's bed.
You just noticed?
How self-involved are you?
If this bed isn't new, then how come
there's plastic on the mattress?
Sometimes I have bad dreams.
Look...
... I just saw my best friend's
brain smeared across the canvas.
It's not gonna be me.
Not me.
That was good.
That was
Tweezers?
-That was really good.
-Thanks.
Any suggestions?
You told him to play the boxer gay?
I might have said...
... "super-gay."
You totally screwed him over.
You're this guy's teacher.
How could you do this?
Because the guy's so good.
And I really, really want this part.
Well, if you really, really want it,
then it's okay.
-Hi, Daddy.
-Baby.
Dr. Greene, how are you?
Thanks for dinner last night.
Thank you for teaching me
a valuable lesson.
Nice hair. What did you do, swim here?
That's it.
I can't take it anymore.
What? He likes your hair and just
wants to know how you got here.
-It's hopeless. I'm just gonna go.
-What?
-I'm sorry. It's just
-Ross?
What's with the neck?
I keep telling him
to go to my chiropractor.
You still going to him?
He couldn't get into
med school in lxtapa!
Thank you.
That's what I keep saying.
Excuse me, Dr. Bobby happens
to be an excellent doctor.
Wait a minute.
His name is Dr. Bobby?
-That's his last name.
-And his first name.
He's Bobby Bobby?
It's Robert Bobby.
And excuse me. He helps me.
-Please. Ask her how?
-What do you need help for?
My alignment.
One leg's shorter than the other.
-Oh, my God.
-Argue with that.
My right leg is two inches shorter!
Come on, you're just tilting!
-Her legs are fine.
-I know that.
-So why do you let her go to him?
-"Let her"?
She doesn't listen to me
about renter's insurance, either.
Wait a minute. You don't have
renter's insurance?
How you gonna run after a thief,
with one leg shorter than the other?
-Would you like some juice?
-I'd love some juice.
This is going so well!
Did you see us? Did you see?
Yeah, honey. I was standing
right there.
Why don't you tell him about
my mole?
Excellent!
There will come a time
in each of your careers...
...when you'll have a chance to screw
over another soap opera actor.
I had such an opportunity
in the recent present.
And I'm ashamed to say...
...that I took it.
I advised a fellow actor
to play a role...
... homosexually.
We both auditioned for the part...
...and as it turned out...
...they....
They liked the stupid "gay" thing
and cast him.
And now...
... he's got a two-year contract...
...opposite Susan Lucci...
...the first lady
of daytime television.
And me?
Me, I'm stuck here teaching
a bunch of people...
... most of whom are too ugly
to even be on TV.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Thank you.
-May I help you?
-Yes, hi.
I'm the lady who got stuck
with the racecar bed.
Look, it's like I told you.
There's nothing I can do.
You signed for it.
"Monica Felula Geller."
All right, we wanna see the King.
Nobody sees the King.
Okay. I'm talking to the King.
Hey, you can't go back there!
Oh, my God.
Hey, watch it, lady!
Hey, good-looking.
All right, I'll leave.
My bed's so boring.